

Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Information Technology]

Notice Period: 2 Months



SOJIMON C Y SOJIMON C Y Reatured 6 Senior Software Developer seeking roles in Software Application, Software Development, Requirement gathering, Configuration Management, Service Delivery, React Js, Redux, Angular, Javascript, CSS and bootstrap

Current Designation: Senior Software Developer

Current Company: UST Global

Current Location: Kottayam

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Kochi, Chennai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Team Lead/Tech Lead

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Senior Software Developer, Team Lead, Software Application, Software Development, Requirement gathering, Configuration Management, Service Delivery, React Js, Redux, Angular, Javascript, CSS and

bootstrap.React.Js.Front End.HTML.CSS

Verified : Le Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

## Summary

Professional experience in developing and designing web applications for 5+ years.

Developed web applications in Angular and React Js.

Developed applications using React native.

Sound Knowledge in React Js, Redux and Angular.

Also worked with technologies like in Javascript, HTML, CSS and bootstrap.

# Work Experience

UST Global as Senior Software Developer Jun 2019 to Till Date

Vanguardcharitable.org (June 2019 - Till Date )

Vanguard Charitable is a public charity sponsored organization for donor - advised funds - a low-cost, tax-effective way to consolidate, accrue and grant assets to charity. Adonor-advised fund is a charitable giving account designed exclusively to invest, grow and give assets to charities for meaningful and lasting impact. This application provide user access the Account Dashboard of their account and get an overview of all relevant details relating to their current balance, available balance, past grant history, pending grants & spawns, investment exchanges, contributions and other transactions. It allows users to make a contribution, to their philanthropic account. Application contains various other functionalities like 'Contribution Activity' page which lists all contribution details, 'Exchange Activity' module containing all exchanges of all for one-time and recurring exchanges, Request a grant agreement, 'Contribution Dashboard' contains all relevant details relating to current balance, available balance, contribution etc. Responsibilities:

Complete Development lifecycle of the 'How it works' and 'Make a Contribution' modules.

Analysis and integration with third party plugins.

Ensure project delivery as per requirements

#### Aveanna

Jan 2017 to Jun 2018

Awanna is the largest provider of pediatric home care which offer pediatric skilled nursing, pediatric therapy, autism service. This application is mainly used to manage all the things like scheduling, nurse verification etc. Using this platform Nurses can apply for various shifts and chat with scheduler for any queries. Features include an easily accessible allocated and available shifts view, a modern chat feature, call and map navigation etc Technologies Used: React Js, Redux, Thunk middleware, Node.js, MySql, Pubnub

#### Responsibilities:

Development of the application layout, Scheduler dashboard, Nurses verification module, Scheduling module etc. Analysis and integration with third party plugins Ensure project delivery as per spelt out in proposal

Tech innovation technologies Pvt Ltd as Software Programmer

# **Important**

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Sep 2016 to Jun 2019

2.) Ritzcarltonyachtcollection.com (July 2018 - June 2019)

Ritz Carlton Yacht collection is a web application used for booking the cruise. The users can find the voyage experiences and various offers and programmes. The voyages are listed based on ports in port page and destination in destination page. 'Find a cruise' page allow user to filter cruise based on region, ports, departure date, price and voyage duration.

Technologies Used: Angular 5, Drupal, Java

Responsibilities:

Development of 'Find a cruise', 'Guest and travel agent dashboards' and 'My reservation' modules.

Analysis and integration with third party plugins Ensure project delivery as per requirements

Ensure project delivery as per requirements

Sysg Soft Technologies as Software Engineer Jul 2015 to Sep 2016

^ Back to Top

## **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Information Technology) from MAHATMA GANDHI UNIVERSITY, KOTTAYAM in 2014

^ Back to Top

## **IT Skills**

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
React Js, Angular, React Native	
Redux, Redux-Saga, JavaScript	
HTML, CSS	
bootstrap, Antd, SCSS	
JIRA	
AGILE	
Git, SVN	
Visual Studio Code, Sublime, Xcode	

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Malayalam	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

## **Work Authorization**

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No** 

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.